Finding Aid for Vice President and Chief Financial Officer (University of Michigan) Records, 1909-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Central Topical Files, 1929-2003
  - 1929-1977, 1955-1975
    - Higher Education
      - Citizens Committee on (Bentley Committee)
        - 1962-1964 (Box 12)
        - 1963-1965 (Box 12)
      - Facilities Act (P.L. 89-752), 1963-1964 (Box 12)
    - Historical Society of Michigan, 1967-1968 (Box 12)
    - Hold Credits, 1970-1973 (Box 12)
    - Hoobler, Sibley re. Bejcek Fund, 1970-1971 (Box 12)
    - Hospital
      - Accounts Receivable
        - 1972-1973 (Box 12)
        - 1974-1976 (Box 12)
      - Administration (Conard Committee) (Box 12)
        [see also "Hospital: Medical Center Planning: Review Committee on Structure"]
      - Blue Cross-Blue Shield, 1972-1973 (Box 12)
      - Budget and Reports to Regents on Finances, 1974-1975 (Box 12)
      - Data Systems Computer (Box 12)
      - Director Search Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
      - Financial Management and Construction History, 1893-1957 (Box 13)
      - Medical Center Planning
        - Building, 1970-1973 (Box 13)
        - Long Range Program Planning, 1965-1970 (Box 13)
        - Planning Study, 1960-1961 (Box 13)
        - Review Committee on Structure, 1968-1974 [see also "Hospital: Administration"] Medical Costs (Educational Costs in a Teaching Hospital), 1963-1966 (Box 13)
      - Medical Service Plan and Professional Fee Income
        - Professional Fee Study, 1969-1971 (Box 13)
        - January-September 1974 (Box 13)
        - October-December 1974 (Box 13)
        - 1976-1977
          - General (Box 13)
          - Policy Committee Materials (Box 13)
          - Policy Committee Report, March 23, 1976 (Box 13)
      - Planning, 1966-1968 (Box 13)
      - Problems, 1976 (Box 13)
      - Replacement Hospital Project
        - Financing, 1972-1973 (Box 13)
        - Survey by Arthur Young and Company on Salaries, 1973 (Box 14)
    - Housing
      - Historical, 1967-1973 (Box 14)
      - Residence Halls
        - Operations, 1947-1962 (Box 14)
        - Rates, 1973 (Box 14)
      - University Credit Union, 1970-1973 (Box 14)
    - Huebner, Gertrude, 1966-1974 (Box 14)
    - Humanities, 1974-1975 (Box 14)
    - Indirect Costs (Federal)
      - Agreements for Research and Educational Services Rates
        - 1958-1969 (Box 14)
        - 1970-1974 (Box 14)
      - General
        - 1945-1952 (Box 14)
        - 1950-1961 (Box 14)
        - 1962-1966 (Box 14)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 14)
        - 1968-1969, 2 folders (Box 14)
        - 1969-1970 (Box 14)
        - 1970-1971 (Box 14)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 14)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 14)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 14)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 14)
    - Indirect Costs (State), 1973-1975 (Box 14)
    - Inglis House, 1959-1973 (Box 15)
    - Institute of Science and Technology, 1957-1963 (Box 15)
    - Insurance
      - Consultant (John Liner Associates), 1971 (Box 15)
      - General, 1972-1975 (Box 15)
    - Insurance (cont.)
      - Malpractice
        - General
          - 1975 (Box 15)
          - 1976, 2 folders (Box 15)
        - Wayne County General Hospital, 1975 (Box 15)
      - Self Insurance, 1957-1973 (Box 15)
      - Unemployment Compensation, 1973-1975 (Box 15)
      - Workmen's Compensation, 1964-1974 (Box 15)
    - Inter-Cooperative Council, 1966-1970 (Box 15)
    - Investment
      - Common Fund, 1971-1973 (Box 15)
      - Corporate Responsibility, 1970-1972 (Box 15)
      - Endowments and Trust Funds
        - 1969-1970 (Box 15)
        - 1970-1972 (Box 15)
        - 1970-1973 (Box 15)
        - 1972-1974 (Box 15)
        - 1973-1977 (Box 15)
      - General, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
      - Loans, 1957-1963 (Box 15)
      - Nelson Endowment Funds, 1976 (Box 16)
      - Reviews
        - 1952-1955 (Box 16)
        - 1956-1959 (Box 16)
        - 1960-1963 (Box 16)
        - 1964-1966 (Box 16)
        - 1967 (Box 16)
        - 1968-1969 (Box 16)
        - 1970 (Box 16)
        - 1971 (Box 16)
        - 1972 (Box 16)
        - 1973 (Box 16)
        - 1974 (Box 16)
        - 1975 (Box 16)
        - 1976 (Box 16)
      - Student Loan Marketing Association, 1973-1974 (Box 17)
      - Total Return Fund, 1967-1972 (Box 17)
      - Uniform Management of Endowment Funds Act, 1971-1976 (Box 17)
    - Japanese Studies, Center for
      - 1973-1974 (Box 17)
      - 1975 (Box 17)
    - Keweenaw Rocket Launch Property, 1962-1972 (Box 17)
    - Labor Relations, Hutchinson Act
      - 1947-1965 (Box 17)
      - 1966-1967 (Box 17)
    - Labor Negotiations
      - 1968 (Box 17)
      - 1976 (Box 17)
    - Land Sale and Acquisition, 1960-1965 (Box 17)
    - Law School
      - 1968-1971 (Box 17)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 17)
    - Lawsuit
      - Act 379 (Labor Mediation Board), 1965-1970 (Box 17)
      - Autonomy
        - 1964-1967 (Box 17)
        - 1968-1971 (Box 17)
        - 1972 (Box 17)
        - 1975 (Box 17)
    - Legal Action, 1965-1967 (Box 18)
    - Legal Opinions
      - 1936, 1967-1972 (Box 18)
      - 1963-1968 (Box 18)
        (abstracts to 1856)
    - Lindermer, Lawrence, 1968-1976 (Box 18)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
      - 1970-1971 (Box 18)
      - 1973 (Box 18)
    - Matthaei, Frederick, Jr. and Sr., 1967-1973 (Box 18)
    - Medical School, Neurosurgery, 1974 (Box 18)
    - Memberships, 1967-1977 (Box 18)
    - Michigan College and University Business Officers
      - 1960-1964 (Box 18)
      - 1965-1967 (Box 18)
      - 1968-1970 (Box 18)
      - 1972 (Box 18)
      - 1973 (Box 18)
      - 1974 (Box 18)
      - 1975 (Box 18)
      - 1976 (Box 18)
    - Michigan Council of State College Presidents
      - Cost Studies
        - 1960-1963 (Box 18)
        - 1964-1970 (Box 18)
      - General
        - 1964-1967 (Box 18)
        - 1974 (Box 18)
      - Joint Capital Outlay, 1958-1960 (Box 18)
    - Michigan Council of State College Presidents (cont.)
      - Manual for Uniform Accounting
        - 1964-1968 (Box 19)
        - 1968-1969 (Box 19)
      - Municipal Services Study, 1968 (Box 19)
      - Space Studies, 1960-1962 (Box 19)
      - Unified Budget, 1959-1965 (Box 19)
    - Michigan Daily, 1967-1968 (Box 19)
    - Michigan Historical Collections
      - 1973-1974 (Box 19)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 19)
    - Michigan League
      - 1951-1965 (Box 19)
    - Michigan Research Foundation, 1965-1974 (Box 19)
    - Michigan Society of Fellows
      - 1969-1972 (Box 19)
      - 1972-1976 (Box 19)
    - Michigan (State)
      - Auditor General [see "Auditor General (State of Michigan)"] (Box 19)
      - Building Authority
        - Capital Outlay, 1957-1964 (Box 19)
        - General, 1957-1967 (Box 19)
      - Reporting Provisions in Appropriations Act, 1975 (Box 19)
      - Reports to Legislature on Campus Properties, 1974 (Box 19)
      - Use and Financing Statements, 1973-1974 (Box 19)
    - Midwestern Universities Research Association (MURA)
      - 1964-1966 (Box 19)
      - 1967-1971 (Box 19)
    - Music, School of, 1970-1974 (Box 19)
    - National Association of College and University Business Officers (NACUBO)
      - General, 1972-1976 (Box 19)
      - Subcommittee on Ethics, 1970-1971 (Box 19)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC), 1981 (Box 19)
    - National Commission on the Financing of Postsecondary Education, 1973 (Box 19)
    - Natural Resources, School of, 1970 (Box 19)
    - North Campus (Box 20)
      - Development, 1950-1965; 4 folders (Box 20)
      - General Services (Water, Sewer, etc.), 1957-1964 (Box 20)
      - Planning, 1959-1960 (Box 20)
      - Property Ownership, 1958-1962 (Box 20)
    - Occupational Safety and Health Act (OSHA), 1973 (Box 20)
    - Ossabaw Island, Georgia, 1962-1965 (Box 20)
    - Organization (J.F. Brinkerhoff), 1971-1972 (Box 20)
    - Osborn, Mrs. Chase, 1968-1975 (Box 20)
    - Parking, 1955-1958 (Box 20)
    - Patents and Copyrights, 1971-1973 (Box 20)
    - Pennsylvania, University of (Study of Dormitory Operations), 1972 (Box 20)
    - Personnel [see also "Policies and Procedures"]
      - General, 1971-1976 (Box 20)
      - Personnel Department, 1971-1976 (Box 20)
      - Professional and Administrative (P&A)
        - Reductions in Force, 1975 (Box 20)
      - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 20)
    - PIRGIM [see "Public Interest Research Group in Michigan"] (Box 20)
    - Planning, Long Range Planning Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 20)
    - Plant Extension
      - Capital Improvements Data, 1950-1958 (Box 20)
      - Committee
        - 1944-1948 (Box 20)
        - 1953-1958 (Box 21)
        - 1963-1966 (Box 21)
        - 1967-1968 (Box 21)
        - 1968-1969, 1969-1970 (Box 21)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 21)
        - 1972-1973, 1973-1974 (Box 21)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 21)
    - Policies and Procedures
      [see also "Personnel"]
      - 1937-1961 (Box 21)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 21)
    - Pollution Control, 1974-1975 (Box 21)
    - Primark, Dr. V.M., 1972-1974 (Box 21)
    - Privacy Act (Federal), Student Records, 1974-1976 (Box 21)
    - Public Interest Research Group in Michigan (PIRGIM), 1971-1976 (Box 21)
    - Regents
      - Conference
        - 1954-1962 (Box 21)
        - 1963-1965 (Box 21)
        - 1967-1973 (Box 21)
      - Retreats
        - 1971-1974 (Box 21)
        - 1975 (Box 21)
    - Research Policies
      - 1957-1971 (Box 21)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 21)
      - 1974 (Box 22)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 22)
    - Reserve Officers Training Corps (ROTC), 1969-1973 (Box 22)
    - Saudi Arabia Consortium Agreement, 1971-1975 (Box 22)
    - St. Joseph Hospital, 1972 (Box 22)
    - SACUA
      - Campus Planning and Development Committee
        - 1950-1958 (Box 22)
        - 1960-1964 (Box 22)
        - 1964-1965, 1965-1966 (Box 22)
        - 1966-1967 (Box 22)
      - Economic Status of the Faculty Committee, 1965-1970 (Box 22)
    - Scholarships, Restricted Trusts, 1969-1970 (Box 22)
    - Self-Liquidating Projects
      - 1955-1964 (Box 22)
      - 1965-1969 (Box 22)
    - Service Centers (Natural Resources and Electrical Engineering), 1968-1972 (Box 22)
    - Sloan Foundation, 1973-1974 (Box 22)
    - Social Work, School of, 1970-1973 (Box 22)
    - Staff Benefits
      - Annuitants Association (Retirement)
        - 1954-1955 (Box 22)
        - 1958-1966 (Box 22)
      - Committee on Annuities
        - 1944-1951 (Box 22)
        - 1951-1959 (Box 22)
        - 1956-1959 (Box 23)
      - Common Stock Appreciation (Retirement Fund), 1967-1969 (Box 23)
      - Disability, 1965-1970 (Box 23)
      - Early Retirement, 1972-1973 (Box 23)
      - Employee Retirement Plan Annual Reports, 1952-1971 (Box 23)
      - Group Life Insurance, 1948-1950 (Box 23)
      - Retirement
        - General
          - 1966-1968 (Box 23)
          - 1968-1971 (Box 23)
          - 1971-1972 (Box 23)
          - 1972 (Box 23)
          - 1973 (Box 23)
          - 1974-1975 (Box 23)
          - 1943-1970 (Box 23)
          - 1945-1963 (Box 23)
        - Older Faculty Members Retirement Fund, 1953-1969 (Box 23)
      - Social Security
        - 1951-1954 (Box 23)
        - 1954-1955 (Box 23)
    - Special Stipends for Academic Personnel (Form G), 1969-1970 (Box 24)
    - Student Aid
      - 1968-1971 (Box 24)
      - 1971 (Box 24)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 24)
      - 1973 (Box 24)
      - 1974 (Box 24)
      - 1975, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Student Bookstore
      - 1969 (Box 24)
      - 1970 (Box 24)
    - Student Driving Regulations, 1968-1969 (Box 24)
    - Student Government Council [Michigan Student Assembly], 1963-1976 (Box 24)
    - Student Services, Office of, 1974-1976 (Box 24)
    - Total Return Fund
      - 1969-1974 (Box 24)
      - 1973 (Box 24)
    - Travel Expense Studies
      - 1954-1973 (Box 24)
    - Trotter House, 1972-1973 (Box 24)
    - Tuomy House, 1967-1970 (Box 24)
    - United States
      - Income Tax Reports, 1968-1972 (Box 24)
      - Service Academies Study, 1974 (Box 24)
      - Tax Reform, 1972-1974 (Box 24)
    - University Club
      - 1955-1968 (Box 24)
      - 1969-1974 (Box 24)
    - University Press (Box 25)
      - 1962-1970 (Box 25)
      - 1970-1976 (Box 25)
    - Utilities
      - 1967-1976 (Box 25)
      - 1972-1974 (Box 25)
    - Van Schaick Foundation, 1963-1966 (Box 25)
    - Vetulonia Project (Archaeological Exploration in Italy), 1961-1963 (Box 25)
    - Wage-Price Guidelines, 1979 (Box 25)
    - Willow Run Airport
      - General
        - 1946-1947 (Box 25)
        - 1948-1949 (Box 25)
        - 1950-1956 (Box 25)
        - 1958-1965 (Box 25)
        - 1966-1970 (Box 25)
        - 1969-1973 (Box 25)
        - 1974 (Box 25)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 25)
        - 1977 (Box 25)
      - Negotiations, 1947-1951 (Box 25)
    - Willow Run Laboratories [see also "Environmental Research in Michigan]
      - 1971 (Box 25)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 25)
    - [Eliminated During Reprocessing] (Box 26)
    - [Eliminated During Reprocessing] (Box 27)
      (continued)
    - [Eliminated During Reprocessing] (Box 28)
    - [Eliminated During Reprocessing] (Box 29)
    - [Eliminated During Reprocessing] (Box 30)
    - [Eliminated During Reprocessing] (Box 31)
    - [Eliminated During Reprocessing] (Box 32)
    - [Eliminated During Reprocessing] (Box 33)
  - 1963-1988, 1977-1988
    In 1990-1991, the Bentley Library accessioned a second subseries of Topical Files containing records from 1963 to 1988 (boxes 59-65). The bulk of this material dates from James Brinkerhoff's tenure as Vice President and Chief Financial Officer (1977-1987). This topical file is arranged alphabetically and includes correspondence, memoranda, and reports. These records reflect some of the financial concerns of the university during that time period and highlight major fiscal decisions made by the university.
    Perhaps the most significant fiscal project faced by the University of Michigan in the early 1980s was the construction of a replacement university hospital. Many of the financial planning records for the new hospital are included in the topical file under "Hospitals - Replacement University Hospital". Financial negotiations with the architects, Albert Kahn Associates, may also be found in this group of folders. (Researchers may also consult the University Hospitals record group for further information.)
    While not officially part of his office's responsibilities, Brinkerhoff participated in several important nationwide university consortiums. The records of his involvement in those organizations are also included in the topical files. As one of the original members of the Association of Universities for Research in Astronomy, Inc. (AURA), the University of Michigan maintained a continued interest in this significant but expensive research venture. The records of Brinkerhoff's service on several financial committees for this consortium from 1979 to 1985 may be found under AURA. Also, researchers interested in the early financial difficulties and eventual solvency of the Research Libraries Group, Inc. (RLG) should consult Brinkerhoff's records as treasurer of this consortium. (For additional materials on AURA the researcher should consult the organization's records and for additional information on RLG the researcher should consult the records of the University of Michigan Library; both record groups are available at the Bentley Historical Library.)
    Several other folders include material of potential research interest. "Ford Presidential Library" includes correspondence, memoranda, and meeting minutes pertaining to the efforts of university officials to locate this library in Ann Arbor. "Health Maintenance Organizations" includes correspondence and reports, beginning in 1968, regarding the feasibility of an HMO at the University of Michigan. "Public Interest Research Group in Michigan" includes information regarding the debate over check-off donations for that group as a part of student registration. Finally, those interested in the demise of the student bookstore should see "University Cellar."
    - Association of Universities for Research in Astronomy, Inc. (AURA), 1977-1988 (Box 59)
      - Board of Directors, 1977-1988; 14 folders (Box 59)
        (includes correspondence and reports)
      - Financial Affairs
        - Audit-Investment Committee, 1979-1984; 5 folders (Box 59)
        - Financial Policies Committee, 1984-1985; 3 folders (Box 60)
      - History and By-Laws (Box 60)
      - Kitt Peak National Observatory, 1975-1981; 4 folders (Box 60)
      - Miscellaneous, 1978-1983 (Box 60)
      - National Solar Observatory, 1982-1983 (Box 60)
      - Sacramento Peak Observatory, 1976-1985; 2 folders (Box 60)
      - Space Telescope Science Institute, 1978-1983; 2 folders (Box 60)
    - Barbour-Waterman Gymnasium, 1977 (Box 60)
    - Budget Authorizations for Special Allocations, 1978-1987 (Box 60)
    - Butterfield Theaters, Inc., 1974-1982; 2 folders (Box 61)
      (includes information on stock sales)
    - Capital Equipment Management Program, 1979-1980 (Box 61)
    - Capital Outlay
      - Historical Record, 1965-1974 (Box 61)
      - Public Works Employment Act, 1976 (Box 61)
    - Chemistry Department Stores, 1975-1977 (Box 61)
    - Coliseum, 1974 (Box 61)
    - Cyclotron, 1969-1977 (Box 61)
    - East Asian Studies, 1975-1983; 4 folders (Box 61)
      (includes information on fund-raising activities)
    - Economics Building Fire, 1982-1984 (Box 61)
    - Environmental Research Institute of Michigan, 1972-1977 (Box 61)
    - Estates
      - Benton, Dwight F., 1982-1984 (Box 61)
      - Herbert, Imogene M., 1973-1975 (Box 61)
      - Hofmann, Arnold E., 1973-1978 (Box 61)
      - Knapp, Arthur D., 1978-1980 (Box 61)
      - Pernt, Alfred, 1975 (Box 61)
      - Robbins, Frank and Edith, 1963-1977 (Box 61)
      - Slater, Ellis, 1982-1985 (Box 61)
      - Spaulding, Florence Tucker, 1967-1973 (Box 61)
      - Turner, Amy Prudden, 1972-1980 (Box 61)
    - Fees, 1975-1977 (Box 61)
    - Flint Riverfront Land Acquisition, 1973-1976; 3 folders (Box 61)
    - Flint Riverfront, General, 1974-1985 (Box 61)
    - Ford Presidential Library, 1976-1983
      - Committee Minutes
        - Building, 1977-1979 (Box 61)
        - Liaison, 1979 (Box 61)
      - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1976-1983; 5 folders (Box 61)
      - Meetings, 1978 (Box 61)
      - Gifts-Contingent, 1968-1980 (Box 61)
    - Handicapped (provisions for), 1971-1973 (Box 62)
    - Health Maintenance Organizations, 1968-1981; 7 folders (Box 62)
    - Henderson House, 1980-1982 (Box 62)
    - Hospitals
      - Former University Hospital
        - Burn Center, 1969-1984; 3 folders (Box 62)
        - Housekeeping Services Contract, 1977-1979 (Box 62)
        - Medical Services Plan, 1975-1980; 3 folders (Box 62)
        - Reorganization, 1974-1976 (Box 62)
      - Replacement University Hospital
        - Albert Kahn Associates, 1980-1987; 2 folders (Box 62)
        - Bond Ratings, 1983; 2 folders (Box 62)
        - Capital Campaign, 1979-1987 (Box 63)
        - Change Orders, 1982-1986; 2 folders (Box 63)
        - Construction Project Manager
          - Selection, 1975-1982; 2 folders (Box 63)
          - Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 63)
        - Equipment Purchasing, 1979-1986 (Box 63)
        - Financing, 1974-1981; 4 folders (Box 63)
        - Miscellaneous, 1979-1985 (Box 63)
        - Parking
          - General Information, 1980-1986 (Box 63)
          - Hospital Advisory Parking Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 63)
        - Planning Consultants, 1984 (Box 63)
        - Project Suspension Strategies, 1982 (Box 64)
        - Schedule Recovery Plan, 1984 (Box 64)
    - Lelong Study (sources and uses of university funds), 1975-1976 (Box 64)
    - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, 1973-1981; 2 folders (Box 64)
    - Patents and Copyrights, 1974-1979 (Box 64)
    - Professional and Administrative Review Task Force (salary structures), 1976-1978 (Box 64)
    - Public Interest Research Group in Michigan (PIRGIM), 1976-1987; 3 folders (Box 64)
    - Regents
      - Correspondence, 1969-1987 (Box 64)
      - Monthly Memos, 1977-1983 (Box 64)
        (outgoing from vice president and chief financial officer)
    - Research Libraries Group, Inc.
      - 1982-1985, 3 folders (Box 64)
      - 1986-1988, 2 folders (Box 65)
    - Shapiro, Harold T., 1979-1987; 2 folders (Box 65)
    - Solar Energy Research Institute, 1975-1976 (Box 65)
    - St. Joseph Mercy Hospital, 1965-1977; 4 folders (Box 65)
      (acquisition of old hospital buildings)
    - Student Employment Program, 1974-1982 (Box 65)
    - Tax Exemption, 1984-1985 (Box 65)
    - Transportation
      - Miscellaneous, 1975-1980 (Box 65)
      - North Campus Buses, 1979-1980 (Box 65)
        (includes complaints about service)
    - University Cellar, 1982-1987 (Box 65)
    - University of Minnesota, 1976-1989 (Box 65)
      (includes comparisons of financial information systems)
    - Willow Run airport, 1977 (Box 65)
      (employee transfers)
    - [Eliminated During Reprocessing] (Box 66)
  - 1925-1989, 1975-circa 1985
    A 1993 accession of Topical Files (Boxes 67-76) covers the years 1925-1989, with the bulk of records dating from the mid-1970s to mid-1980s. The contents of this accession parallel those of boxes 59 through 65.
    The files document the Vice President and Chief Financial Officer's response to several major trends which affected the university during the 1970s and 1980s. First among these is the response to growing financial constraints. The impact of state budget cuts and attempts to deal with a scarcity of funds may be seen in the "Broadcasting and Media Services," "Energy Conservation," "Research," "Student Aid," and "University Press" files, while the increasing sophistication of fund-raising efforts is documented in the various "Capital Campaign" folders.
    The financial and administrative response to another major trend, technological change, is evident in the "Computing Center," "Information Systems Design and Optimization System Project," and "Telecommunications Planning" files.
    The "Labor Relations" files, some of which have been restricted for thirty years to protect the privacy of individual university employees, give a sense of the often strained relationship between labor and management, particularly during the 1970s. The "Ann Arbor/University Relations," "North Campus Planning" and "Parking" files document various issues which affected relations between the university administration and the city of Ann Arbor.
    - Accounting, Misc., 1975-1986; 2 folders (Box 67)
    - Administrative System, General, 1977-1983; 2 folders (Box 67)
    - Administrative System-Security, 1978-1986 (Box 67)
    - Ann Arbor/University Relations, 1969-1984; 2 folders (Box 67)
    - Audits
      - External Auditor Selection, 1986 (Box 67)
      - Outside Auditors, 1971-1986; 8 folders (Box 67)
      - Reports to Regents, 1977-1984; 4 folders (Box 67)
    - Audit-Reports to Regents, 1985-1986 (Box 68)
    - Audit-Response to Auditor General Report, 1974 (Box 68)
    - Bank Negotiations-Automatic Teller Machines, 1977-1978 (Box 68)
    - Bendix Property, 1973-1986 (Box 68)
    - Biological Station, 1975-1983; 2 folders (Box 68)
    - Broadcasting and Media Services, 1978-1987; 2 folders (Box 68)
    - Brown, George H. (Catherine S. Brown Memorial Fund), 1962-1983 (Box 68)
    - Budget, misc., 1985-1988 (Box 68)
    - Burton, Marion LeRoy Memorial Fund, 1977 (Box 68)
    - Business Administration Capital Campaign, 1981-1984 (Box 68)
    - Business Administration, misc., 1982-1985 (Box 68)
    - Camp Knight Property, 1977 (Box 68)
    - Campaign Policy Committee, 1986-1987; 9 folders (Box 68)
    - Capital Campaign, 1978-1989; 11 folders (Box 69)
    - Capital Campaign, General Motors, 1981 (Box 69)
    - Capital Campaign, meeting with Bob Barrett (re: Gerald Ford), 1982 (Box 69)